所以你真的会与芝加哥警署
So this really something you're doing
-每个警员都这样做吗  -是的  长官
- with every officer from CPD? - Yes, sir.
你不用叫我长官
Hey, you don't have to call me sir.
不用这么正式
It's pretty formal for somebody
毕竟你都要问我最深最黑暗的秘密了
who's gonna ask me my deepest, darkest secrets.
不会的  我保证
It won't be that, I promise.
我只会问你一些
I'm simply asking questions
对预测将来有帮助的问题
designed to forecast future problems.
预知未来吗
To predict the future?
那应该很不错  是吧
Oh, that'd be nice, wouldn't it?
可惜不是
But no.
这只是早期干预策略的一环
This is just another supplement to Early Intervention Strategy.
对  要预测我是否会在未来工作中
Right, to predict if I'm gonna do something stupid
犯一些愚蠢的错误
on the job in the future.
这纯粹是支持  而不是惩罚
It's purely supportive, not punitive.
我如果答错了呢
What if I answer a question wrong?
答案没有对错
There is no wrong.
都是为了让我们更加理解你
Any answer would just help us understand you.
-理解你是谁  -我懂
- Who you are. - Well, I get that.
我以前接受过心理咨询  来吧
I've been to therapy before, so lay it on me.
你的咖啡一般怎么喝
So how do you like your coffee?
黑咖啡
Black.
你呢
How do you like yours?
我不喝咖啡
I don't drink coffee.
你一直是这么喝吗
And have you always taken it that way?
是的  一份奶一份糖  每天早上都是
Yes, one cream, one sugar, every morning.
这能说明我什么特点吗
Does that say something about me?
你觉得自己是个墨守陈规的人吗
Would you consider yourself a creature of habit?
不会  我什么都能喝
Uh, no, no, I drink all the drinks.
你用过种族歧视的词汇吗
Have you ever used a racial slur?
这个话题太突然了  我没有
That's a hell of a segue. No, no I have not.
你听过家庭成员使用种族歧视的词汇吗
Have you ever heard a family member use a racial slur?
不知道  也许吧
I don't know. Maybe.
有过
Yeah.
对于你自己和家庭成员的关系
Would you say you have a good relationship
-你认为融洽吗  -我觉得还行
- with your family? - I'd say it's fine.
你认为警察是你的家人吗
Do you consider the police force your family?
我的部门是
My unit.
其他警员呢
And the rest of the police force?
不  只是同事
No, coworkers.
你是否有过
Have you ever felt
可以称之为愤怒管理问题的经历
what you would categorize as anger issues?
没有
Nope.
创伤经历呢
And what about trauma?
有
Yes.
你体会过创伤后的压力吗
Have you experienced post-traumatic stress?
体会过
Yes.
你在工作中犯过错误吗
Have you ever made a mistake on the job?
你开过枪吗
Have you ever had to fire your weapon?
你杀过人吗
Have you ever killed someone?
你在工作中恐惧过吗
Have you ever felt fear on the job?
你是否认为自己不适合这份工作
Do you believe you are the wrong fit for this job?
作为芝加哥警署的一名警员
Are you proud to be an officer
你是否感到自豪
of the Chicago Police Department?
人人影视
原创翻译  双语字幕
字幕组招新中
请访问 YYSubs.com
你是否认为自己有能力  有价值  有正义
Do you believe you're capable, worthy, right?
翻译    青椒   nemonini    哈里不是波特
他们问这些问题
What the actual hell do they think
到底是想得到什么啊
they're gonna get out of all of that?
要是想知道我是不是好警察
They should check my police record
直接看我的警局档案就可以了
if they wanna know if I'm a good or a bad cop.
翻译    Carolgcz   苏葵*4
是不是  对吧
Am I right? Am I?
不  他们不想知道你现在如何
Nah, nah, they don't wanna know who you are now.
他们是想知道你以后如何
They wanna know who you gonna be then.
校对    苏葵
你跟他们待一小时  也神神叨叨的了
One hour with them, and you're a psychic too?
也许我有潜力
Maybe I got the future in me,
但如果回答问题能够帮助我们找到偏见
but if asking us questions is gonna help us find prejudice,
时间轴    Jenny   西查   chance-coco
避免问题  改善执法现状
prevent problems, and progress policing,
我愿意坐一整天
then I'll sit for it all damn day.
我理解他们的意图
I get the intention.
后期    8T
我只是觉得有点过了  不是吗
It's just, I don't know, seems a little overzealous, right?
我只是想说  别为了找到少数
I'm just saying, you don't punish the many
而滥罚无辜  你懂吗
to get to the few, you know?
总监    苏葵
为了找不存在的裂缝  折磨无辜的好警察
Grill good cops looking for cracks that ain't there.
我只是想知道  我对咖啡的喜好
I just wanna know what my coffee order
-跟当警察有关系吗  -各位
- has to do with anything. - Hey, guys.
怎么了  有案子吗
What's going on? We got a case?
一场涉及警员的枪击案
An officer-involved shooting.
-很糟糕  -不是吧
- A bad one. - No.
发生了什么
What happened?
我一个巡警哥们
A buddy of mine in patrol
发来了居民拍下来的视频
sent over this civilian witness video.
有人拿手机拍了
Somebody caught it on a cell phone.
我说了  把双手完全举起来
I said get your hands all the way up
转过身去
and turn around.
别拿枪指着我
Stop pointing your gun at me!
举起手来  转过身去
Hands up! Turn around!
你拿枪指着我  而我什么都没做错
Your gun is pointed at me, and I did nothing wrong.
我拒绝
So no.
我说最后一次  好吗
Then this is the last time. Okay?
举起手来  远离武器
You're gonna get your hands away from your weapon,
然后转过身去
and you're gonna turn around.
韦兰  你别激动  好吗
Hey, hey, Wheelan, let's just relax, all right?
我不动  我知道自己的权利
I'm not moving. I know my rights.
打电话给你上级
Call your supervisor.
把手从武器上拿开
Hey, hands away from your weapon, up!
我的手根本没靠近武器
Mine aren't nowhere near my weapon!
-举起手来  -我们冷静下
- Get them up! - Let's just calm down.
-转过身去  -我绝对不动
- Turn around! - I ain't gonna move.
-我让你转身  -韦兰
- I said turn around! - Wheelan!
-快点  -韦兰
- Now! - Wheelan!
快
Now!
我的天哪
Oh, my God!
不要
No!
那孩子死了吗
The kid die?
死在了人行道上
On the pavement.
他是谁
Who was he?
他叫杰夫·邓肯  没有前科
His name is Jeff Duncan. Zero priors.
在腰带上持有一把合法枪支
Had a legal gun in his waistband.
因为超速被喊停车
Pulled over for going seven over the speed limit.
惠特尼·杨高中毕业
Graduate of Whitney Young.
目前在芝加哥大学就读
Student at University of Chicago.
警员呢
And the officers?
开枪的培训官  叫戴维·韦兰
The FTO who fired the shot, Dave Wheelan.
旁边的警员刚警校毕业一个月  叫安德烈·库珀
PPO a month out of the academy is named Andre Cooper.
库珀说了吗
Cooper's talking?
跟事件响应小组和民警问责办公室都说了
Oh yeah, to IRT and COPA,
他的证词从未改变
and his statement never changed.
杰夫压根就没有去掏枪
Jeff never went for his weapon.
完全没有理由去使用致命手段
There was zero justification to use deadly force.
我还有三名目击证人
I also have three witnesses
外加两个警用监控
and two POD cameras.
内务部正在去韦兰警官家的路上
IAD is on their way to Officer Wheelan's house now,
但我希望找两名便衣
but I would like two undercovers
来帮助押送他
to make the transport.
那...  那不是我团队的工作
That's... That's not what my unit does.
我是说想找个芝加哥警官
I mean I think you'd be hard pressed
愿意掺和到这件事
to find any Chicago police officer
-恐怕很难  -我明白
- who wants to step in this. - I know.
我明白过去的经验告诉我们
I know history tells us that this
这种事是不能介入的
is not something to step in,
所以我才找我信任的团队
which is why I'm asking a unit I trust,
我也希望他们能信任我
and I hope trusts me.
这个视频我看了有三十多遍  汉克
I've watched this footage three dozen times, Hank,
州检察官也是
as has the SA.
这件事已经很清楚了
And it's as clear as this moment ever comes,
是不良用枪行为
it was a bad shoot.
你能找两名警官吗  博伊特警长
Can you spare two officers, Sergeant Voight?
视频还没有在网上疯传
The video's not yet viral,
但我们会让所有警官立即进入12小时工作状态
but we will be putting every officer on immediate 12s.
我们预计会有大量示威和暴力情况
We expect mass protests and violence,
因此我们要行动迅速
so we will move fast.
阿特沃特警官  鲁塞克警官
Officer Atwater, Officer Ruzek,
我要求你们前往韦兰警官的家
I want you to go to Officer Wheelan's home
以杀人罪逮捕他
and arrest him for murder.
芝加哥警署
第八季  第八集
戴维·韦兰警官  从警三十年
Officer Dave Wheelan, on the job 30 years,
16次局内表彰  一年只有1次投诉
16 department commendations, only one complaint a year.
你想怎么念他的事都行  但听好了
You can read about him all you want, but listen to me:
你们就是代步车  明白吗
you're both nothing more than an Uber, okay?
宣读他的权利  逮捕他
Read him his rights, arrest him,
开车载上他  把他放到南区拘留所
drive him, drop him off at south detention.
你们什么都不用做  什么都不要说
You do nothing, you say nothing.
千万不要掺和进去
Do not get involved.
会让你们作证时惹麻烦的话
Not one word that can get you in trouble
一个字都不要说
if you have to testify,
-听明白了吗  -嗯
- you understand me? - Yeah.
好  车已经准备好了
All right, car's been cleared.
没有警察标记的
It's unmarked.
应该是别的部门来干的
Should be another unit doing this.
我觉得任何好警察
I feel like any good cop
都应该能去逮捕这种警察
should be able to arrest a cop like this.
我感觉这个档案太少了  不可能是全部
I mean this file's real sparse. This can't be the whole of it.
把他弄得像是个在常规停车检查时
It makes him look like a good cop
杀死个孩子的好警察似的
who murdered a kid at a routine traffic stop.
常规是没错
Yeah, routine all right.
他家里没有枪
He didn't have guns in the house.
他有个妻子和孩子  她们会很激动
He's got a wife and kids. They're gonna be all emotional.
-琳内特  -二位好
- Hey, Linette. - Hi, guys.
-想象一下杰夫·邓肯的家人吧  -我想过了
- Imagine Jeff Duncan's family. - I have.
只不过我们不是去杰夫·邓肯家
Only we're not going to Jeff Duncan's house
-去抓人的  -谢谢  琳内特
- to arrest nobody. - Thank you, Linette.
不用客气
Yeah. You're welcome.
听着兄弟  我理解这个情况
Look, brother, I know that this is a situation
可能会让我们面对很多种不同情况
that can spin us in a lot of different ways.
大部分情况都不在我们的能力范围内
Most of those ways are above our pay grade.
因此就像博伊特说的  这事与我们无关
So like Voight said, this got nothing to do with us.
我们就去像抓罪犯那样逮捕他
Let's just go arrest this guy like the criminal he is,
不节外生枝  回来该干嘛干嘛  好吗
nice and easy, get back to doing our real jobs, yeah?
收到
Copy that.
杀人犯
Murderer!
不要吧
Come on.
逮捕的事显然是走漏风声了
Well, the arrest clearly leaked.
他们知道我们要来
Knew we were coming.
我的搭档在里面  我只是想和他谈谈
My partner's in there. I just wanna talk.
那个是韦兰的培训生吗
Is that Wheelan's trainee?
喂  不要碰我
Hey, man. You're not gonna touch me,
不要命令我走开  好吗
and you're not gonna tell me to walk away, all right?
我有权来这
I have every right to be here.
他应该被强制休假
He should be on mandatory leave.
凯文  我们走
Come on, Kev. Let's go.
没事  都没事吧
It's all right. Hey, we all right?
我只是想知道他为什么对他开枪
Hey, I just need to know why he shot him.
我们私下聊聊好吗
Can we have a minute?
来吧  库珀  对吧
Come on, man. Cooper, right?
-对  -阿特沃特  鲁塞克
- Yeah. - Atwater, Ruzek.
你没进去过吧
You ain't been in there, have you?
没有  我明白我不应该进去
No, I haven't. I get that I shouldn't.
没错
You should not.
听着  我当时就在场
Hey, yeah, man, I was right there.
我就站在他身旁
I was right there next to him.
我和那哥们一起巡视一个月了
I rode with that dude a month.
兄弟  我就是需要明白这是为了什么
Brother, I just need to know why.
你知道为什么
You know why.
而且你知道你应该回家去  离开这吧
And you know you gotta go home. Get out of here, man.
没事的  有我们呢
It's okay, we got it.
走吧  我们几分钟后就回来
Come on. We'll be back in a few.
别耽搁太久啊
Don't take too long.
韦兰太太吗  我是鲁塞克警官
Mrs. Wheelan, I'm Officer Ruzek.
这位是阿特沃特警官
This is Officer Atwater.
我的天  进来吧
Thank God. Come in.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们的电话一直响个没完
Our phones have been ringing nonstop.
韦兰
女士
Ma'am.
你丈夫呢
Where's your husband?
他在楼上陪孩子们  他们吓坏了
He's upstairs with the kids. They're scared.
这是什么情况  你们是警察兄弟会对吗
What is this? You're with the FOP, right?
我认为你们是来帮我丈夫的
I assume you're here to help my husband.
不
Uh, no.
安妮  我猜他们是来逮捕我的
Annie, I'm guessing they're here to arrest me.
-不  -戴维·韦兰  你被逮捕了
- No. - David Wheelan, you're under arrest.
-你下来好吗  -不
- Can you step down please? - No.
爸爸  什么情况啊
Dad, what's going on?
听着  我只有一个请求
Kay, look, I only got one ask.
别让我孩子看见  去外面再拷我
Okay, spare my kids, huh? Cuff me outside.
可以
Yeah, we can do that.
规定要求我们在屋里拷上你
Protocol is that we cuff you inside.
-转过身  -凯文...
- Turn around. - Kevin...
凯文...  当着孩子呢
Kevin, uh... kids around.
你身上有武器吗
Do you have any weapons on you?
-没有  -这是他的外套吗
- No. - Is this his jacket?
凯特  亲爱的  不会有事的
Hey, Katie, sweetheart, it's gonna be fine.
戴维·韦兰  你因为涉嫌谋杀
Dave Wheelan, you're under arrest
-杰夫·邓肯而被捕了  -好吗
- for the murder of Jeff Duncan. - All right?
好吗  带你妹妹上楼去
Kay, take your sister upstairs.
-戴维  -扎克  带她上楼去
- Dave. - Zach, take her upstairs.
-我该怎么办  -回房间  凯蒂
- What am I supposed to do? - Go to your room, Katie.
我会没事的  亲爱的
It'll be fine, honey.
你有权请律师
You have a right to an attorney.
如果你没有律师  会有...
If you do not have an attorney, one will be...
我什么都没做  你知道吗  我什么都没做
I did nothing. You know what, I did nothing.
你们很快就会接到电话  我已经打给律师了
You're gonna get a call soon. I already called an attorney.
-我什么都没做错  -别说话
- I did nothing wrong! - Stop talking.
当时我有生命危险  我什么都没做错
My life was in danger! I did nothing wrong!
我做了我的工作  下次我还是会这么做
I did my job, and I'd do it again!
-别说话  -我是无辜的
- Stop talking! - I'm innocent!
退后
Back up!
快走  快走  快走
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
退后  离车远点
Back up! Get away from the car!
请远离这辆车  女士
Please step away from the vehicle, ma'am.
退后  退后
Stand back. Hey, hey, back up.
冷静  鲁塞克  冷静  鲁塞克
Easy, Ruz, easy, Ruz, easy.
你刚才怎么回事
What the hell was that?
我说的是真相  因为他们需要听到真相
The truth. Because they need to hear it.
亚当  凯文
Adam, Kev?
在  海莉  我们已经逮捕了人
Yeah, Hailey, we made the arrest.
-正在转送疑犯  -我们有麻烦了
- We're in transit. - We got a problem.
有段我们不知道的视频
There's a video we didn't know about.
杰夫·邓肯在手机上装了个软件
Jeff Duncan had an app on his phone
录下了交警拦车的事
that recorded the traffic stop
并把完整的视频发给了他所有的紧急联络人
and sent the full video to all of his emergency contacts.
有多少人看到了这个视频
How many people saw the video?
已经在网上疯转了
It's gone viral.
总部  市政厅  监狱和南部拘留所
We've got unruly crowds at headquarters, City Hall,
都有很多疯狂的民众
the jails, and south detention.
我们收到了针对韦兰的死亡威胁
We got death threats against Wheelan.
好  海莉  你找我们什么事
Okay, Hailey, what are you telling us here?
你们还不能把他带回来
I'm saying you can't bring him in yet.
除非我们把这里的人赶走  抱歉
Not until we clear this out. Sorry.
安全屋
离你们10分钟车程有个安全屋
There's a safe house about ten minutes from you.
我马上把具体信息发给你们
I'm gonna send you everything right now.
你们就待在那里  我们会尽快搞定  好吗
Just stay there, and we'll be quick, all right?
好  收到
Okay. Copy that.
快把手铐打开
Hey, come on with these cuffs, huh?
我的血液循环都切断了
They're cutting off my circulation.
-我的肩膀都没知觉了  -来
- I can't feel my shoulders. - Here.
谢谢
Thanks.
把你的外套穿上
Put your jacket on.
这应该是其他组的活  哥们
Should be another unit doing this, man.
这里还挺不错
This ain't too bad, huh?
一般只是间破汽车旅馆的房间
Usually it's just a crappy motel room somewhere.
把手伸出来
Put your hands out.
你在开玩笑吧  这里只有我们三个人
Oh, you gotta be kidding me. It's just us three here now.
嗯  你以为我们在这里会怎样
Yeah, what'd you think was happening here?
把手伸出来
Put your hands out.
过去  坐下  我们应该不会在这里待太久
There. Sit. We shouldn't be here long.
好
Yeah.
我们根本就不该来这里
We shouldn't have to be here at all.
我来这里是因为一段拍下我工作过程的视频
I'm here over a video showing me doing my job.
拜托  哥们
Come on, man.
我们来这里是因为一群暴徒想要你的命
We're here because a mob of people want your head.
所以别废话了  好吗
So cut out all the commentary, all right?
我知道你们看到我时怎么想
I get what you think you're seeing when you look at me.
种族歧视的混蛋白人警察  对吗
Some racist white cop prick, right?
但视频自会说明一切
But the video speaks for itself.
当然会
It sure does.
你对我们说的每句话都可能
You know, anything you say to us
成为对你不利的证据
can be used against you,
所以我们都保持安静如何
so how about we just all stay quiet?
不  看看那个视频
No. Watch the video.
你们没看到完整的视频
You didn't see the full thing.
看看吧  看完整的视频
So go ahead and watch all of it.
我知道你想看  看看吧
I know you want to. So watch it.
行
Yeah.
好吧
All right.
驾照  行驶证  保单
License, registration, and proof of insurance?
为什么要拦我的车
Why am I being pulled over?
超速行驶  先生
Driving above the posted speed limit, sir.
拜托  我没开那么快
Come on, I wasn't going that fast.
这是例行的交警拦截  先生
This is just a routine traffic stop, sir.
你去副驾驶侧就行
Just cover the passenger side.
我说最后一次
Last time.
驾照  保单
License and proof of insurance.
警官  我没超速  我不知道这是什么...
Officer, I wasn't speeding. I don't know what this is--
注意语气
Ah, ah, ah. Hey, watch the tone
冷静  让我完成我的工作
and calm down so I can do my job.
就这么回事
That's what this is.
你的工作就是骚扰别人吗
Is harassing people your job?
因为我感觉就是这样
'Cause that's what this feels like.
而且说明一下  因为我正在录像
And for the record, because I am recording this,
我合法地在腰带上别了一把枪
I am legally carrying a firearm in my waistband.
我钱包里有张持枪许可证
I have a concealed carry permit in my wallet.
好  我需要你
Okay, I'm gonna need for you
马上下车
to step out of the vehicle now.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
我被捕了吗
Am I being arrested?
我给你下令了  下车
I just gave an order. Step out.
叫你上司来  我不下车
Call your supervisor. I'm not moving.
为什么用枪指着我
Why the hell is a gun pointed at me?
下车
Step out of the vehicle.
韦兰  长官  我们冷静下
Wheelan, sir, let's just calm down.
是啊  韦兰  冷静
Yeah, Wheelan. Calm down.
从车上给我下来
Step out of the damn vehicle.
-搜车  -你得有搜查令才能搜车
- Search the car. - You need a warrant for that!
长官  这是入侵式搜查
Sir, that's an intrusive search.
小鬼  搜车  否则就等着被开吧  快
Kid, do it or find a new job, now!
举起手来  转过身去
Hands up! Turn around!
你拿枪指着我  而我什么都没做错
Your gun is pointed at me, and I did nothing wrong.
-我拒绝  -我说最后一次
- So no. - Last time.
举起手来  远离武器
Get your hands up, away from the weapon,
然后转过身去
and turn around.
韦兰  你别激动  好吗
Hey, hey, Wheelan. Let's just relax, man.
我不动  我知道我的权利
I'm not moving. I know my rights.
打电话给你上级
Call your supervisor.
转过去  把手从武器上拿开
Turn around. Hands away from the weapon!
我的手根本没靠近武器
My hands are nowhere near my weapon!
-我们冷静下  -转过身去
- Let's just calm down. - Turn around!
我绝对不动  你开枪打我吧
I ain't gonna move so you can shoot me.
快
Now!
我们冷静下  韦兰
Let's just calm down. Wheelan--
快
Now.
你这下看到了吧
You see now?
他不听从命令
He wouldn't comply.
他有敌意
He--he was hostile,
他携带武器  他还动了
he was armed, and he moved.
我担心自己的生命安全  就采取了行动
I feared for my life, and I acted.
你是想告诉我...
You mean to tell me all--
海莉没说给我们增援吧
Hailey didn't say we were getting backup, did she?
趴下
Get down!
有两个枪手
We got two shooters!
低下头  跟着我
Get your head down. Follow me.
低下头  低头  过来
Keep your head down. Head down, come on.
上车
Get in the truck.
-凯文你掩护我  -我掩护我掩护
- Kev got me, you got me? - I got it, I got it, I got it.
-他们在屋里  鲁塞克  -上车  伙计
- They're in the house, Ruz.. - Get in the truck, dude.
快走  快走  快走
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
-好了吗  -好了
- You got it? - Yeah.
-狗娘养的  -该死
- Son of a bitch. - Damn.
呼叫指挥中心  有人开枪袭警
10-1, 10-1! Shots fired at the police.
低下头
Keep your head down.
还有一个枪手
We got another shooter!
我们安全了吗  我们安全了吧
Are we clear? Tell me we're clear.
是的  没人跟来
Uh, yeah. No tail, no follow.
他们想杀了我
They're trying to kill me!
我打中其中一个了  至少有两名杀手
I shot one of them. There's at least two shooters.
把手铐打开  打开
Take these cuffs off. Take them off.
-我是警察  跟你们一样  -闭嘴
- I'm a cop, same as you! - Shut up!
-天啊  -你们听得到吗
- God. - Tell me you got your ears on!
-警长  我们的人遭到了伏击  -什么
- Sarge, our guys got ambushed. - What?
收到
I'm here.
你们没事吧  我在无线电上听到了整件事
Are you okay? I heard the whole thing over the radio.
对  有人袭击了安全屋
Yeah, somebody hit the safehouse.
他到底是什么意思  袭击
What the hell does he mean, hit?
-你们怎么样  -我们没事
- Are you all right? - Uh, we're fine.
我们打中了其中一个杀手  或者两个
We hit one of the shooters, maybe two.
两人都带着面具
Both were masked.
那地方的信息显然被泄露了
I mean, the place was clearly compromised.
他们是去那里杀韦兰的
They were there to kill Wheelan.
亚当  你们还在安全屋吗
Adam, are you still at the house?
不不不  我们离开了
No, no, no, we're driving.
巡逻队说他们一分钟就到
Patrol said they were a minute out,
但是现在离开感觉更安全
but driving feels safer right now.
我们现在到安全屋去  看看是什么情况
Okay, we are heading to the safe house now, see what we can learn.
找到地方停车  等我们派人保护你们
Find a location off road, hang tight until we get you an escort,
只用无线电设备通讯
and use only your DCs to communicate.
好的  收到
All right, copy that.
-喂  鲁塞克  车库  -好
- Yo, Ruz. Garage. - Yeah.
我没受伤  把手铐打开
I wasn't hit. Take the cuffs off.
-转过去  -我没受伤
- Turn around. - I'm not hit.
你们不能把我带去另外一个安全屋
But you know you can't take me to another safehouse
因为他们在第一个安全屋找到我们
'cause if they found us at the first one,
就能找到下一个
they're gonna find us at the next one.
他们在追杀我
They're hunting me!
我们现在到底怎么办
What the hell do we do now?
事情很不对头
There's something very wrong here.
那些枪手找到了安全屋
Those shooters just made a safehouse.
我知道  我们现在要问问自己
I know. What we gotta do is ask ourselves this question:
是有内鬼吗
was it an inside job?
只有芝加哥警署的人知道安全屋的位置
Only people that know about the safehouse is CPD.
更不用说他们比巡逻队早两分钟到
Not to mention, they just beat patrol by two minutes.
好吧
All right.
我想现在最安全的做法就是我们保密
I think the safest thing is we keep this between us,
秘密地带他走
we take him off book,
到没人知道的地方去
we take him somewhere nobody knows about,
直到我们搞清楚到底是怎么回事
till we can figure out what the hell's going on,
到底谁在追杀他
who the hell's hunting him.
秘密地带他走
Take him off book.
老大  我们有个计划  不用护卫队了
Boss, we got a plan. Disregard that escort.
收到
Copy that.
什么情况
What are we looking at?
看起来阿特沃特正中他要害
Looks like Atwater caught him center mass.
-知道姓名吗  -还不知道
- We got a name? - No, not yet.
他们刚把他照片打印出来  不过我们运气好
They just printed him, but I'm thinking we're gonna get a pop.
他有监狱纹身
He's got prison tats.
请看这个
Let me show you this.
子弹壳是.32口径的
There's .32 caliber shell casings here.
这边一路过来都是9毫米口径的子弹壳
Got 9 mil casings all the way over here.
过道过去都有血迹
And then there's blood going down the gangway.
第二个杀手跑了  但是他受伤了
So the second shooter, he's in the wind, but he's injured.
他们两个都有机关枪
So they both had street sweepers.
对  他们相互配合
Oh, yeah, they were coordinated,
但他们不担心交火  破釜沉舟的亡命之徒
but they didn't care about crossfire. This is a do or die crew.
-看来不是十几岁的菜鸟  -不是
- We're probably not looking at teenage foot soldiers. - No.
米勒什么时候到的这里
And when did Miller get here?
她比我们先到
She got here before us.
喂  你过来看一下
Hey, can I show you something?
长官
Ma'am.
兄弟们  给我们点空间
Guys, give us the room.
-你有手下的消息了  -是的
- You heard from your guys? - I have.
-他们没事吧  -没受伤
- Well, they all right? - No injuries.
他们现在在哪
Where are they?
我不知道
I don't know.
他们在秘密转移韦兰
They're transporting Wheelan off book.
电话关机了
They turned their cells off.
他们跟你一起做的决定吗
And they made that call with you?
是的  听着
They did. Look.
如果韦兰或者任何平民有一丝可能
My men are not gonna bring Wheelan in
在路上挨枪子儿
if there is any chance that he or any civilian
我的手下都不会把他带过来
could take a bullet while en route, okay?
你要是想就我们刚刚
You need to try and give me an order
踏入的政治丑闻而下令  请便
'cause of the political dirt we just stepped in, go ahead.
我到这里来是因为我拉你入了泥潭
I'm here because I had you step in the dirt with me.
我不会给你任何命令
I'm not giving you any orders.
无论你们怎么决定  都是最终决定
Whatever your call is, that's the call.
与此同时
In the meantime,
我派人去调查芝加哥警署可能存在的泄密人了
I got a team digging into a potential leak at CPD.
你相信我  汉克
You trusted me, Hank.
我也相信你
I trust you.
好了  你现在得把我的手铐打开
Okay, you need to take my cuffs off now.
没人会帮你打开手铐  别再说了
Nobody's taking them off. Stop asking.
我不能坐以待毙  像畜生一样
I'm not gonna be a defenseless animal.
-坐下  -我不是罪犯
- Sit down. - I'm not the criminal here.
不是吗  那谁是
No? Who is?
你打死的那个19岁的黑人小孩吗
The 19-year-old Black kid you shot down?
我是自卫
I defended myself.
防一个大学生
From a college student?
我有权自卫
I had the right to defend my life.
自卫什么
From what?
凯文  别争了
Kev. Don't.
不  自卫什么
No. From what?
我刚看了视频  你让我看的
I just watched the video. You told me to.
你杀了一个孩子
You murdered a kid,
你还要站在我面前  大言不惭地说你是自卫
and you're gonna stand here in front of me and defend yourself?
-别管了  -别管了
- Just let it go. - Let it go?
他也站在你面前
He's standing in front of you too.
我的意思是  我们可能要在这待上一阵
All I'm saying is, we might be here a while.
这些争吵都帮不上忙  仅此而已
None of this is helping. That's all I'm saying.
别管了  他不值得
Let it go. He's not worth it.
把我的手铐打开  你知道我是对的
Uncuff me. You know I'm right.
我想先跟你把话说清楚  兄弟
I wanna make something really clear to you, man.
我们带你来这的唯一原因
The only reason we brought you here
是保护你不被暗杀
was to keep you from being assassinated.
这不意味着我们有人认为你是无辜的
It doesn't mean either of us think that you're innocent.
坐下
Now sit down.
赶紧
Now.
鲁塞克和阿特沃特不能离开
Ruzek and Atwater can't move
直到我们确认泄密的人不是自己人
until we determine that leak wasn't inside,
并抓到第二个枪手
and we got that second shooter in custody.
所以谁想要戴维·韦兰警官的命
So who the hell is going after Officer Dave Wheelan?
手机技术人员刚把死掉抢手的
Hey, mobile techs just sent over the fingerprint card
指纹卡送来  雷·麦克斯  25岁
on our dead shooter. Ray Macks, 25.
帮派组证实他是死神帮的人
Gangs has him hooked up with the Rollin' Reapers.
他的老大  TJ·琼斯
His boss, T-J Jones,
刚好是杰夫·邓肯的继弟
just so happens to be the half-brother of Jeff Duncan.
TJ的帮派都是职业杀手
T-J runs a crew of hired guns.
他们把自己视为"帮派警察"
They think of themselves as the "police of gangland."
所以TJ的继弟被一个警察杀了
So T-J's half-brother gets killed by a police officer,
然后他派了两个手下去杀那个警察
and he sends two of his guys to kill that police officer.
他保持着街头秩序
He's keeping order on the street.
我们有TJ的东西吗
We got anything on T-J?
没有  没有公开逮捕令  没有假释
No, no open warrants, no longer on probation,
我很怀疑他是否有枪
I seriously doubt he's carrying.
帮派组已经盯上他有一阵了
I mean, Gangs has been on it for a while,
但没找到任何能逮捕他的证据
but they have nothing to arrest him on.
好吧  但他肯定认识第二个枪手
Yeah, well, he knows our second shooter,
无论如何我们要让他跟我们开口谈
so we're gonna make him talk to us anyway.
杰  你和我走  拿上卷宗
Jay, you and me. Grab that file.
好
Okay.
我们只是来找TJ的
We're just here to talk to T-J.
喂
Yo.
TJ
T-j.
你知道我们会来  是吗
You're expecting us, huh?
我弟弟被你们的人杀了
My brother was murdered by your people.
我希望你们是为了这件事而来
I'd hope you'd come for that,
如果这是你来的原因
if that is why you came.
我们想让你去警局和我们谈谈
We want you to come in and talk to us.
没有目击者  我不和警察谈话
I don't talk to police without a witness.
听着  在这里有这么一大帮人盯着
Listen, talking out here with all this...
我是不会同意的
It's just not gonna work for me.
那我猜我们别谈了
Then I guess we won't talk.
你没有可以逮捕我的证据
You don't have anything to arrest me on.
对  确实没有
No, I don't.
这是你朋友汤姆吧  汤姆·格雷根  对吧
Is this your friend, Tom? You Tom Greggin', right?
也叫格雷格
AKA Gregs.
你刚假释两个月
You're two months into probation.
那是沃尔特·卡尔明  六个月
That's Walter Culmin. Six months.
这又是谁  那是吉米·马基
Who we got out here? That's Jimmy Markey.
拉塞尔·沃尔  你跟两个孩子一起生活  对吧
Russell Wall, you got your two kids living with you?
我还知道这是乔·哈特  他妈靠他生活
And I know this is Joe Hart, who's got his mom living on his dime.
我还能继续说
I could keep going,
但显然你喜欢和重罪犯人交好
but it's pretty clear you're all fraternizing with felons.
假释官已经在路上了  除非我们让他们别来
We've got parole officers on their way unless we call them off.
不如你来警局和我们谈谈
What do you say you come in and talk,
这样不用毁了所有人的生活
so we don't have to keep ruining everyone's day?
我被捕了吗
Am I under arrest?
没有
No, sir.
-还是把我的律师叫来  -好的
- Call my lawyer anyway. - Yeah, got you.
接着拍
Keep filming.
你知道他是谁吗
You know who he is?
不知道
Nope.
雷和另外一个人
Ray and a second man
想要杀死一个囚犯和两个警察
tried to kill a prisoner and two cops.
雷现在死了
Ray is dead now,
另一个人逃走了
and the second guy got away.
我们得找到他们
We need to find them.
你知道他是谁吗
Do you know who he is?
不知道
No.
他不为你工作吗
He doesn't work for you?
你没派他和雷去杀韦兰吗
You didn't order him and Ray to kill Wheelan?
没有
No.
两小时前你在哪
Where were you two hours ago?
在图享上跟我女友视频
Live on the Gram with my girl,
但你们早就知道了
but you know that already.
我自愿把手机给你们了  你们问我要的
I willingly gave you my phone. You asked.
我猜你和女友打电话时一定不好受
I imagine that call with your lady friend must've been rough.
就那样失去了你的继弟
I mean, losing your half-brother like that,
又死了一个黑人  被警察击毙
another Black man gone, shot by a cop.
我懂
I get it.
真的
I do.
TJ  那个警察要面临谋杀指控
T-J, that cop was being brought in on murder charges.
你明白吗  谋杀
You understand? Murder.
芝加哥警署一定会严办这件事
CPD is doing this one right.
我希望你能够
One thing I would appreciate
别再把杰夫称为我的继弟了
is if you wouldn't call Jeff my half-brother.
他就是我弟弟
He was my brother.
我的血肉
My blood.
你们关系很好  我们理解
You guys were close. We understand that.
但枪击警察  TJ
But shooting at the cops, T-J?
这不是办法
Not the right move.
为了伸张正义  就算是我们警察也得信任系统
To get justice, even us cops have to trust the system.
这是我们的唯一
It's what we got.
这是你们的唯一
It's what you got.
这是你们的系统
It's your system.
我们的系统不保护你的社区
Our system doesn't protect your neighborhood.
所以你保护  对吧
So you do, right?
我没这么说
I didn't say that.
但信任系统
But trust the system?
你愿意花五十万信任系统
You willing to bet half a billion on that
而不是给警察渎职买单吗
instead of paying police misconduct bills?
我觉得如果你们好好看看自己
I think if you both looked at yourself,
我们会得出同样的结论
we'd know the same thing.
你们在我们的社区蹲点并不是为了保护我们
Y'all ain't in my neighborhood camped out to protect us.
你们在那只是为了确保
Y'all only there to make sure
我们这些人不流窜到城市的其他地方
we don't leak out into the rest of the city.
但我没枪击谁  我从不开枪打人
But I shot no one. I never shot anyone.
我都没有枪
I don't even own a gun.
你没有我的任何证据
You have nothing on me.
所以我想走了
So I'd like to go now.
他的不在场证明很完美
His alibi's rock solid.
他绝对不是第二个枪手
He's definitely not our second shooter.
他的律师来了吗
Hey, did his lawyer show yet?
来了  他已经威胁要起诉我们了
Yeah, he's already threatening to sue.
他说我们非法带TJ来警局
He says we brought T-J in unlawfully,
他要求我们立即释放他
and he wants a release right away.
那TJ的手机呢
What about T-J's phone?
一无所获  我们下载了所有东西
We're good there. We downloaded everything.
几乎全是一次性电话联系人
It's mostly burner phone contacts.
那家伙很聪明  但组织犯罪技术部正在查
The guy's really smart, but our OCD techs are on it.
好  好
Okay, okay.
那我们就放了他
So we'll release him.
但在他车上放个追踪器  让战术小队待命
Just get a tracker on his car and put a tac team on it too.
我们要动用所有资源
We're gonna take everything we got
并彻底核查TJ手机上的内容
and put it up against everything in T-J's phone.
相信我  第二个枪手
Believe me, that second shooter
就躲在那其中
is gonna be buried in there somewhere.
找到他
Find him.
好  雷·麦克斯
All right, Ray Macks.
-他是其中一个枪手  你认识他吗  -不认识
- He's one of the shooters. You recognize him? - No.
-那好  TJ·琼斯  -不认识
- All right, T-J Jones. - Nope.
你在恩格尔伍德待了三十年
You've been in Englewood 30 years,
你说你从没见过这些面孔吗
and you're going to tell me you've never seen those faces?
当然  我见过好多次这些面孔
Sure, I've seen those faces a bunch of times.
行  这算是个开头
Okay, that's a start.
你告诉我他们帮派里还有谁
You tell us who's in their crew.
不  我是说我见过那些表情
No, I mean I've seen those faces.
那些"我恨警察"的表情
The "I hate cops" faces.
你在恩格尔伍德和谁有私人恩怨吗
Do you have any personal beefs in Englewood?
拜托  帮帮我们
Come on, man. Help us out here.
当然  我们都有
Yeah, yeah, we all do.
我工作的地方  就是警察对抗其他人
Where I work, it's us versus them.
我们一出现  他们就觉得是侵占军
We show up, they see an occupying force.
不  不是我们所有人
Nah, not all of us.
得了吧  兄弟
Oh, come on, man.
当然  每次我们出现
Sure, every time we show up,
就有了剑拔弩张的关系
we starting a bad relationship.
你知道为什么吗
You know why?
我们是穿着警察制服  带着警徽和枪的
We're the city's secret thoughts and fears
城市秘密想法和恐惧
dressed in blue with badges and guns.
对  我爸以前也爱说这种屁话
Yeah, my dad used to say the same stupid thing.
直到我们抓到第二个枪手  否则我们不能离开
We cannot leave here until we get this other shooter in custody.
-我知道  -那帮帮我们
- I know that. - Then help us.
我在帮你们  但我不知道名字  懂吗
I am helping you out, but I don't have any names, all right?
他们就向我开枪了
They're just shooting at me
因为我在尽我的职责  你懂吗
because I was doing my job, you got that?
-你的职责  是吗  -没错
- Your job, huh? - That's right.
-是吗  -对
- Yeah? - Yes.
你说说你的职责是什么
Explain your job to me.
-我不想死  -别说这些
- Hey, I didn't wanna die. - There's no talking.
-所以我...  -闭嘴
- So I did-- - Shut up!
听好了
Listen up.
米勒办公室刚确认泄密人不在警局内部
Miller's office just confirmed the leak was not from inside CPD,
第二个枪手查的怎么样了
so where are we at with that second shooter?
快查到了
We're close.
组织犯罪技术部调出了TJ手机里的所有号码
OCD tech pulled all the numbers from T-J's phone.
只有11个也在死去枪手的手机上
Only 11 of those were also on the dead shooter's phone.
其中五个  包括死去抢手的电话
Five of those, including the dead shooter's,
是在三个月前一起购买并激活的
were purchased and activated together three months ago.
-我们猜是TJ买的  -好  懂了
- We're guessing T-J got them first. - Okay, I got it.
只有一个号码的所有信号位置
Only one number pinged to every tower
跟死去抢手的手机一致
alongside the dead shooter's phone.
这肯定是第二个枪手
This has gotta be our guy right here.
-好  找到这手机现在在哪  -好
- Okay, find out where that phone is now. - Yup.
大伙  我刚和组织犯罪技术部打完电话
Hey, guys. I just got off with OCD tech.
他们终于找到了一些监控录像
And they finally got something from POD footage.
八个监控摄像头拍到了这个银色SUV
A silver SUV was caught on eight cameras.
它停在戴维·韦兰家一条街区以外
It was parked a block away from Dave Wheelan's house.
然后拍到了它跟在阿特沃特和鲁塞克
Then they caught it at two stoplights
车后的两个红绿灯处
behind Atwater and Ruzek,
然后是它停在我们的安全屋外
and then it's right out front of our safehouse.
-所以是跟车  -对
- Okay, it was a physical follow. - Yeah.
这辆车登记在安托奈特·克拉克名下
The car is registered to an Antoinette Clark.
她22岁  住在恩格尔伍德
She's 22, lives in Englewood.
霍斯特德  把地址给我
Halstead, give me that address.
63街和马奎特街交汇处
It's 63rd and Marquette.
第二个抢手的电话信号现在就在那里
That's where our second shooter's phone is sitting right now.
-把那人抓来  -走
- Get that guy in custody now. - Let's go.
芝加哥警署  开门
Chicago PD. Open up.
-你是安托奈特·克拉克吗  -没人报警
- Antoinette Clark? - No one called the police.
他在这吗  他伤害你了吗
Is he in there? Did he hurt you?
没人伤害我  你们没有搜查令
No one hurt me. You don't have a warrant.
我不用让你们进来  都没人报警
I don't have to let you in. Nobody even called you.
安托奈特  我们知道他受伤了
Antoinette, we know he's hurt.
我们能帮忙
We can help.
他还在流血  对吧
He's still bleeding, isn't he?
他是一小时前被击中的
He was shot hours ago.
如果他还在流血  那他就快死了
If he's still bleeding, then he's dying.
你知道的
You know that.
我负责她
I got her.
有枪
Gun.
5021G  马奎特街6850号需要救护车
5021 George, I need an ambo to 6850 Marquette.
枪伤受害者
GSW victim.
收到  5021G  已派救护车
Copy that, 5021 George. Ambo on the way.
听着  我只是说说  好吗
Look, I'm just saying, okay?
我保护了这些人三十年
Three decades I protected those people,
现在就因为我被拍到尽警察的职责
and now I'm getting judged for five minutes on a video
我就要被人评头论足
showing me being police.
-你听到这家伙的话了吗  -我试着不听
- You hear this dude? - I'm trying not to.
...但这家伙不是那样
...but this guy wasn't that!
好吗  他从一开始就不配合
All right? He was not compliant from the start!
拜托  我只是  拜托
Please, I just-- Please.
我们忽略他就好了  保持冷静
Let's just ignore him. Stay calm.
为什么
Why?
为什么我要保持冷静  为什么你这么冷静
Why am I keeping calm? Why are you so calm?
你怎么能和我坐在那
How can you just sit there with me
听着他为自己狡辩
listening to this man defend himself
仿佛我们没看到视频一样
acting like we didn't just see the same tape?
哥们  那枪不该开  你还想让我说什么
Bro, I--it was a bad shoot. What do you want from me?
我只想熬过今天  好吗
I'm just trying to get through this, okay?
我只想回家
I just wanna go home.
我不想搅合超出我们能力范围的事
I don't want to get involved in things that are above us.
仅此而已
That's all!
我来告诉你我们不该做什么
Let me tell you what we ain't gonna do.
我们不该说这超出了我们的能力范围
We ain't gonna say this is above our paygrade.
我们不能忽略这人是害群之马
We are not going to dismiss this man as one bad apple
就因为我们都是警察  懂吗
because we are in this, all right?
-我们不能躲在...  -躲在什么后面
- We got stop hiding behind-- - Behind what?
身为白人
Being white.
身为白人  真的假的
Being white? Really?
不是黑人也能分辨黑白对错
You don't gotta be Black to know wrong from right.
我从没说过那人做的事正确
I never said that anything that that man did was right.
你听到我说了吗
Did you hear me say that?
想想这个白人做的事
Think about what this white man did
然后当你去他们中间出警时
and how the next Black kid is gonna look at you
-下一个黑人小孩会怎么看你  -我知道
- the next time you go out there. - I know.
我知道  但我现在不和你争论
I know, but I'm not doing this with you right now.
为什么
Why not?
为什么  我们在这里
Why not? We're here.
不如就敞开说说  我们被枪击过
We might as well. We have been shot at,
被追赶过  都是为了保护杀害黑人小孩的
chased down, all while protecting the white cop
白人警察  而我还得接受这一切
that killed the Black kid, and I gotta live with that.
你为什么不
Why not you?
我生气  你为什么不
I gotta be angry. Why not you?
因为你是个善良的白人警察
'Cause you the good white cop
无法感同身受吗
that can't understand?
谁都与这事脱不了干系
Who has nothing to do with any of this?
你就想说这个吗
Is that what you're trying to say?
因为我不是  我不是这样的人
Because I don't! That's not me.
他内心的丑恶不代表我
What's inside of him is not inside of me,
而你最应该明白这点
and you should be the one to know that!
你怎么敢说这样的话  兄弟
How dare you, man!
我受够了你一天到晚质疑我
I'm sick of you questioning me all the time.
为什么是我
Why is it me?
为什么我得替那个家伙做出解释
Why is it me that has to answer for this guy?
你问问自己那个问题
Huh? Ask yourself that question!
对  你瞧
Yeah, you see?
他知道我是无辜的
He knows I'm innocent.
闭嘴
Shut up!
你知道我是
You know I am,
你的老爸也会这么说
and your old man would say the same thing.
别跟我提我爸的事
Do not talk to me about my father.
好吧  我担心自己有生命危险
Okay, yeah. I feared for my life.
你根本没有生命危险
Your life wasn't even in danger!
而你觉得事发时我感觉不出来吗
And you don't think I can feel when it is?
我在战区当了三十年警察
I did 30 years in a warzone.
你知道我逮捕过多少开枪的人吗
You know how many men I put away who shot
然后等他们回到街头
then got right back out on the street
又开枪打人吗
and shot again?
我抱过多少过垂死的孩子
How many dying kids I held in my arms?
有多少子弹从我头顶呼啸而过
How many bullets went past my head?
而你的意思是  当我生命受威胁时
And you're gonna tell me that I don't know
我感觉不出来吗  是吗
when my life is danger? Huh?
我认为自己有生命危险
I feared for my life!
你害怕杰夫·邓肯
You feared Jeff Duncan.
你看到另一个人黑人拿着枪
You saw another Black thug toting a gun.
得了吧  这从来都跟种族根本没关系
Oh, man, it had nothing to do with race ever!
这就是种族的问题
It everything to do with it.
杰夫不肯配合  好吗
Jeff was noncooperative, okay?
你也看到了
And you saw that.
不  我看到了一个男人
No, I saw a man who lost empathy
他不再同情自己宣誓服务和保护的人
for the people he swore to serve and protect.
-他拒绝...  -我看到一个心惊胆战的人
- He resisted-- - I saw a man who was scared.
-他...  -害怕那些人
- He was-- - Scared of those people,
而你在开枪之前就已经害怕了
and you were scared way before you even pulled the trigger.
我当时有生命危险
My life was in danger.
你不能这么狡辩  这次不行了
You ain't gonna do that. Not this time.
你不能责怪死去的黑人受害者
You're not gonna defend yourself
来帮自己辩白
by blaming a dead Black victim.
你看看
Look at that.
我们冷静下  韦兰
Let's just calm down. Wheelan!
快
Now!
你干了什么
What did you do to it?
这  这不是原视频
That--that ain't the video.
他动了  他伸手去拿武器了
He moved. His hand moved for his weapon.
他的手动了
It moved!
-他没动  -不  他动了
- He did not move. - Yes, he did.
等等  你篡改了吗
What, did you alter it?
你篡改了
You altered it.
你为什么要这么做  你为什么这么做
And why would you do that? Why would you do that?
我知道他动了  好吗
I know he moved, okay?
因为我看见了  他动手了
'Cause I saw him move. He moved.
韦兰
Wheelan.
他没动
He never moved.
你为什么会觉得他...
What on Earth would make you think he--
亚当  凯文  我们抓到第二个枪手了
Adam, Kev. We got the second shooter.
你们安全了
You're all clear.
带韦兰回来吧
You go ahead and bring Wheelan in.
收到
Copy that.
我们只需要你配合
We just need you to cooperate.
我不想回答你的问题
I don't wanna answer your questions.
好  跟我说说
All right, talk to me.
是蝎式冲锋枪
It's a Scorpion.
我赌十倍赔率这就是袭击安全屋的枪
Ten to one it's a match to our hit.
我找到了枪手的手机
I got the shooter's phone.
汉克  这手机上有追踪信号
Hank, there's a tracking signal on this phone.
激活中吗
Active?
对  而且它在追踪一辆车
Yes. And it's tracking a vehicle,
信号还与他人分享了
and the signal's being shared with someone else.
有一条已发送的信息
There's an outgoing message.
"去不了了  出血加重
"Can't go. Bleeding's worse.
-你去干掉韦兰"  -这是另一个枪手
- You take Wheelan." - It's another shooter.
凯文  鲁塞克  好好听着
Kev, Ruzek, listen to me close.
现在有个枪手正在追踪你们
You got on an active shooter tracking you right now.
找掩护  我们马上来
Take cover. We're on our way.
可能是韦兰的一个手下
Probably one of those people at Wheelan's.
好的  收到
All right, copy that.
他怎么能给你们的车装追踪器
How the hell did he get a tracker on your car?
人群敲击这辆车的时候
When they were banging on the car,
他们可能趁乱放了追踪器
they probably placed a tracker.
我们得赶紧离开这里
We gotta get the hell out of here.
我们得走了  凯文  找到了吗
We gotta go. Kev, you got anything?
-找到了吗  凯文  -找到了
- Anything, Kev? - Got it.
总部  总部  罪犯向警方开枪
10-1, 10-1, shots fired at the police.
收到
Copy that.
走走走
Go, go, go.
我得换子弹
I gotta reload.
凯文  车里还有多余弹夹吗
Kev, we got any extra mags in the car?
没了  兄弟  我们就是个代步车
Naw, man, we were supposed to be a damn Uber.
该死
Damn.
-我们得撤退了  -快
- We gotta retreat, man. - Come on.
走走  我来
Go, go, go. I got it.
快走  快走
Move, move, move.
-好  走走  -掩护我  掩护我
- All right, move, move! - Cover me, cover me!
蹲下  赶紧
Stay down! Come on!
快  快
Come on, come on.
5021I  三名便装警察步行
5021 Ida, three plainclothes officers on foot.
警官受到重火力袭击  被困在这里了
We are taking heavy fire, we are pinned down.
130街和尤因街  我们需要后援
130th and Ewing. We need backup.
收到  马上过去
Copy, cars are rolling your way.
其他人不要用无线电
Everyone stay off the air.
蹲下  知道吗
Stay down, all right?
你看到有几个枪手了吗
You got eyes on how many shooters?
-就一个  -可能还有其他人
- One. - There could be more.
我没看到其他人
I ain't see anybody else.
-给我一把枪  -嘘  安静
- Give me a gun. - Shh, shh.
这地方有几个门
How many doors on this place?
就两个
Just the two.
我们不能从那边出去
Well, we can't go out that way.
我们被困在这里了
We're stuck right here.
我没子弹了  你还有几发
I'm out of ammo. How many rounds you got?
两三发吧
Two or three.
你得赶紧把我手铐摘了
You gotta take my cuffs off now.
不  别说话  别说话了
No, stop, stop, stop talking. Stop talking.
-我不要这样死掉  -我们不会的
- I'm not gonna die like this! - We're not.
后援已经来了  你得住嘴了
Backup's on the way. You gotta stop talking.
我们等到后援来  我就解开你的手铐
We get clear for a sprint, I'll uncuff you.
这里不止有我们
We're not alone.
过来  过来
Come over here, come on.
调度中心  我们静音了
Dispatch, we're going dark.
我只想要那个杀了我弟弟的人
All I want is the man who killed my brother!
我会为这件事而死
I'll die for that!
但告诉我
But tell me this:
你们愿意为韦兰吃子弹吗
are you willing to take a bullet for Wheelan?
让他出来  我就放了你们
Leave him now, and I'll let you walk away.
他是个凶手
He's a murder!
这肯定是你们做过最简单的决定了
This is the easiest decision you're ever gonna have to make!
留下他  你们走
Leave him, you walk!
你们留下  就得一起死
Stay, you die with him!
你知道我能瞄准
You know I have the shot.
留下他
Leave him!
放下武器
Drop the weapon!
举起手走出来
Come out with your hands high!
他在上面  右侧角落
He's upper level, right corner.
只有他  只有一把枪
It's just him. There's one weapon.
引开他的火力  我去他那边
Draw his fire. I'll move.
准备好了吗
Ready?
走  走
Go, go.
韦兰  快来
Wheelan, move!
留下我吧
Leave me.
什么
What?
你们离开这里  好吗
Just get the hell out of here, okay?
没人会知道的
No one will ever know.
我是认真的  快走
I'm serious. Go!
听着  听着
Listen, listen.
他停止开枪的唯一原因
The only reason for him to stop shooting
是为了移动到我们的上方
is because he's trying to get on top of us.
-我需要你别动  -好吧  听着
- I need you to stay down. - Okay, listen.
我  你说得对  我害怕了
I was--you were right. I was scared.
好吗  我害怕了
Okay, I was scared.
我不知道为什么
I don't know why,
但他看到了  好吗
but he saw it, okay?
我杀了那个孩子  对吧
I murdered that kid, didn't I?
别动
Stay down.
我说了留下我
I said leave me!
等等  让我来处理
Hang on! I got this.
我在这  我在这
Here I am! Here I am!
别动  凯文  你还好吗
Stay down. Kev, you good?
-凯文  -我没事
- Kev! - I'm good.
我没事
Yeah, I'm good.
韦兰
Hey. Wheelan!
不行  你不能死
Uh-uh. Not like that.
不行  这样太轻松了
Uh-uh. That's too damn easy.
这样太便宜你了  挺住
That's too damn easy. Come on.
你不能就这样死了
You ain't gonna go out like that!
你不能
Not you!
不能这样
Not like that.
-鲁塞  你还好吗  -看着我
- Ruz, you good? - Look at me.
还好  在上面
Yeah, up top.
-警长  我上去  -挺住
- Sarge, I'm gonna go up. - Come on.
挺住  韦兰  挺住
Come on, Wheelan. Come on.
他死了  凯文
He's gone, Kev.
这不公平  这不公平
It's not fair. It's not fair.
太便宜他了
That's too easy.
没事的  你尽职了
It's okay. You did your job.
我的心理测评回来了
Mm, I got my psych results back.
"鲁塞克警官对警局
"Officer Ruzek has an uncompromising loyalty
坚定的忠诚  可能是个问题"
to the police force. This could be problematic."
那这个呢  "阿特沃特警官对他的同僚
How about, "Officer Atwater has a lack of trust
"缺乏信任
"for his fellow officer.
这可能是个问题"
This could be problematic."
"恰到好处的忠诚
"Appropriate loyalty,
"值得赞许的同情心
"Commendable level of empathy...
恰到好处的保护服务意识"
Appropriately tempered to protect and serve."
他们也让你做测试了吗  警长
They made you take the test, Sarge?
那些是戴维·韦兰的测试结果
Those were Dave Wheelan's results
一周前
a week ago.
人性深不可测  你知道吗
People are a thousand things, you know?
你让他们干这行  在这个系统里
You throw them in this job, this system,
一瞬间
one moment,
一眨眼  你做的决定
you know, blink of an eye, what comes out...
就是最终决定
Comes out.
你要怎么阻止一件事
I mean, how are you supposed to stop something
如果你都没有察觉到
you can't see coming?
是啊
Yeah.
你们今天干得都很好
You both did good today.
我猜我也该回家了
I guess I should be getting home too.
你还好吗
You good?
我还在这
I'm here.
韦兰认为杰夫动了
Wheelan believed Jeff moved.
他发誓看到了没发生的事
Swore he saw something that didn't happen.
韦兰不知道自己是那样的人
Wheelan didn't know he had it in him.
如果你也没察觉呢
What if you can't see it coming?